Guide to the Jack Underhill papers, 1963-1997
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 10: Books, 1969-1984; (5.5 boxes)
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 4, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    84.2
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 5 (2 copies), 1980 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    84.3
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 6, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    84.4
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Unidentified p.78-79, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    84.5
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 4, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    84.8
  - New Community Development Corporation 1980 Appropriations Subcommittee Hearings Witnesses' Briefing Book (Box 59, Folder 7)
    122.6
  - New Community Development Corporation 1981 Appropriations Subcommittee Hearings Witnesses' Briefing Book (Box 60, Folder 1)
    122.5
  - New Community Development Corporation 1982 Appropriations Subcommittee Hearings Witnesses' Briefing Book (Box 60, Folder 2)
    122.4
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 3, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    83.7
  - Underhill Book Draft Review-Chapter II Section 3, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    84.6
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 3, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    84.7
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 4, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    83.8
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II sections 4 (Grant Michell reviewer), 1983 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    85.1
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 5 (2 copies by 2 reviewers), 1983 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    85.2
  - Underhill Book Draft Review-Chapter II Section 5 (2 copies by 2 reviewers), 1983 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    85.3
  - Underhill Book Draft Review-Chapter II Section 3 (Washington Monthly 7 Dunn Reviewer), 1983 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    85.4
  - Underhill Book Draft Review-Chapter II Section 3 (Lessley Wiles reviewer), 1983 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    85.5
  - Underhill Book Draft Review-Chapter II Section 3 (Grant Mitchell reviewer), 1983 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    85.6
  - Underhill Book Draft Review-Chapter II Section 3 (Grant Mitchell), 1983 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    85.7
  - Underhill Book Draft Review-Appendix III "Travel in New Communities...!", 1983 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    85.8
  - Visions, Illusions and Perceptions: The Story of Soul City (Thesis), 1984 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    118.7
  - Bibliographies, 1980s (Box 61, Folder 8)
    128.2
  - Bibliographies, 1980s (Box 62, Folder 1)
    128.3
  - Bibliographies, 1980s (Box 62, Folder 2)
    128.4
- Series 11: Oversize, 1980; (1 folder)
  This series includes about 29 sheets. All the maps are for New Towns. The maps are all located in map drawer no. 1 which is separate from the rest of the collection.
  - Flower Mound-Dallas Ft. Worth area, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    4 sheets; 149.1
  - Jonathan, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    3 sheets; 149.2
  - St. Charles, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    4 sheets; 149.3
  - Radisson, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    1 sheets; 149.4
  - Woodlands, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    3 sheets; 149.5
  - Shenandoah, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    3 sheets; 149.6
  - Columbia, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    4 sheets; 149.7
  - Newfields, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    1 sheets; 149.8
  - Kingwood, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    3 sheets; 149.9
  - Kingwood, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    3 sheets; 149.8
  - Harbison, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    5 sheets; 149.10
  - Maumelle, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    2 sheets; 149.11
  - Park Forest South, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    4 sheets; 149.12
  - Roosevelt Island, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    1 sheets; 149.13
  - Cedar Riverside, 1980 (Box Mapcase, Folder 1)
    2 sheets; 149.14